

Profile

Junior web developer, specialized in modern web.

Knowledgeable in Front-End, UI and UX and equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Proficient and certified in an assortment of technologies, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Type Script, SQL, PHP, currently learning Python.

Bringing forth several years of experience and expertise in leading a team up to 15 people . Accustomed to working well with others and committed to project guidelines.

Employment History

Owner, Baketo, Bogotá

OCTOBER 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2022

Manager of Engineering area, Moraequipos SAS, Bogotá

MAY 2017 - OCTOBER 2020

Full time Mother, Bogotá

DECEMBER 2015 - OCTOBER 2017

Researcher of new lines of business, Moraequipos SAS, Bogotá

MARCH 2015 - DECEMBER 2015

Improvement process manager, Ilko Peru SAC, Lima

SEPTEMBER 2014 - FEBRUARY 2015

Education

Modern Web Developer, W3 Schools

AUGUST 2022 - JANUARY 2023

Front-End Developer, W3 Schools

AUGUST 2022 - NOVEMBER 2022

Industrial Engineering, Universidad de Los Andes, Bogotá

AUGUST 2009 - MAY 2014

Courses

Negotiation, Universidad de Los Andes

JULY 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2018

Management control, Universidad de Los Andes

JANUARY 2017 - MARCH 2017

Project Evaluation and Management, Universidad de Los Andes

JANUARY 2016 - MAY 2016

Details

Bogotá Colombia

+57 302 201 2043

gaby@bygabymora.com

Links

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Github

Twitter

WhatsApp

www.bygabymora.com

Skills

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

React.js (with Hooks)

Type Script

SQL/MySQL

Bootstrap

Mui Component Library for

React.js

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Leadership Skills

Fast Learner

Ability to Work in a Team

Languages

English

Spanish; Castilian